most of you know me is a dirty
degenerate hippie who lives in a van and
wear [__] he finds in abandoned houses
which is all true but what you did not
know meletus is that I also have a
string of vacation rentals and
destination locations throughout the us
today I'm going to show you my Tennessee
location Joe's tree Retreat check it
out it has exposed beams everywhere and
I painted this thing to look like a tree
cleus one bedroom upstairs with the most
badass bathroom in all of Appalachia
mother [__] dig Special by none other
than Austin aens himself peekaboo views
of pond mountain right here off the
front
porch and he double covered porches wrap
all the way around for some goddamn
great Front Porch
Sitting it even comes with this on
coffee maker see ain't got to go to the
gas station to buy coffee dog case y'all
didn't notice from my seashack I kind of
got a thing from Green
cabinet downstairs we got two bedrooms I
get door our cleus this last bedroom is
my favorite
for obvious
reason God damn man downstairs there's
this nice ghetto ass bathroom I built in
the laundry room so you ain't got to
take your drunk ass up them spiral
staircases to try and pissing ni
[__] so if you want to have a
kickass time in a kickass house and a
kickass place with some kick ass woods
and a kickass host just call the host
with the most felonies Joe come stay at
my tree Retreat DM me for a 10% coupon
code [__]